There's you know a couple different
places you have the organic engines
where you're scoring in that realm
and then of course you have The
paid for paid -to -play type
systems paying to play is going to
depend on your
business model what
sphere you happen to be in and if
in fact
It's really crowded then that's
going to be really expensive to try
to get into that realm
and then it depends on how many
clients convert typically and then
how many of those clients You're
able to retain and have you know
you utilize their business or you
them utilize your business And then
what you're charging whether this
stuff is going to make sense
Overall to you on the other end of
it